export const data = [
  {
    question: "How do you pass props to a React component?",
    option1: "By using the arguments object.",
    option2: "By using the props object.",
    option3: "By using the this keyword.",
    option4: "By using the state object.",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the primary purpose of CSS?",
    option1: "To add structure to a web page",
    option2: "To define the behavior of web elements",
    option3: "To style and layout web content",
    option4: "To create interactive elements on a web page",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the correct syntax for a JavaScript function?",
    option1: "function myFunction()",
    option2: "function: myFunction()",
    option3: "define myFunction()",
    option4: "create function myFunction()",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a popular JavaScript framework?",
    option1: "React",
    option2: "Node.js",
    option3: "Python",
    option4: "MySQL",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the alt attribute in an <img> tag?",
    option1: "To specify the image file format",
    option2: "To set the height and width of the image",
    option3: "To add a border to the image",
    option4: "To provide an alternative text description for the image",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the `async` keyword in JavaScript?",
    option1: "To declare a function that returns a promise",
    option2: "To indicate that a function is asynchronous",
    option3: "To define an asynchronous function that doesn't return a promise",
    option4: "To make a function execute in the background",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which CSS property is used to control the spacing between lines of text?",
    option1: "letter-spacing",
    option2: "line-height",
    option3: "word-spacing",
    option4: "text-align",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the correct syntax for creating a class in JavaScript?",
    option1: "function MyClass {}",
    option2: "class MyClass {}",
    option3: "defineClass MyClass {}",
    option4: "new MyClass {}",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the useState hook in React?",
    option1: "To create custom hooks.",
    option2: "To define a component.",
    option3: "To access the DOM.",
    option4: "To manage state within a functional component.",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the DOCTYPE declaration in HTML?",
    option1: "To specify the character encoding of the document.",
    option2: "To indicate the version of HTML being used.",
    option3: "To define the title of the document.",
    option4: "To set the language of the document.",
    answer: 2,
  },
];
